# **ADARSHA**

K

#### SYSTEM ENGINEER

PHONE I (+91) 7353896072

EMAIL I adarshakl33@gmail.com

LOCATION I Bengaluru, INDIA

**EXPERIENCE I** 3 Years 7 Months

## **Key Skills**

- Cloud
- AWS
- AWS Cloud Practitioner
- Angular
- Object Oriented Programming
- Java
- SQL
- Angularjs
- Node.Js
- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS
- MySQL
- lam Security
- Jdbc Database
- SAML
- Okta
- SSO
- Mean Stack

# Languages

Hindi

### **Profile Summary**

3.7 years of experience in Information technology, which includes demonstrated work experience in the design and implementation of enterprise-wide security applications and work experience in Angular version 7 and above, skilled in HTML, CSS, and Agile Methodology, AWS development.

### **Work Experience**

### **System Engineer**

Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) 10/2023 - Present

At Tata Consultancy Services, I specialize in developing TypeScript code for generative Al models, collaborating with data scientists to meet project requirements. I utilize AWS CDK to replicate and troubleshoot error scenarios, enhancing model training through prompt engineering. My role involves optimizing scripts for the efficient and scalable training and deployment of Al models using AWS services. I am actively involved in the end-to-end Al development process, ensuring continuous improvement and seamless integration of TypeScript scripts.

#### Senior Systems Engineer

Infosys

01/2021 - 01/2021

Almost 2.5+ years of experience in Information technology, which includes demonstrated work experience in the design and

- English
- Kannada
- Tamil
- Telugu

### Social links

 www.linkedin.com/in/adars ha-k-203558160 implementation of enterprise-wide security applications and work experience in Angular version 7 and above, skilled in HTML, CSS, and Agile Methodology.

### Senior Systems Engineer

Infosys

01/2021 - 09/2023

#### Education

B.Tech/B.E. Electronics/Telecommunication
2020

Vivekananda College of Engineering and Technology, Puttur

Grade - 8.06/10

**12**th 2016

> Karnataka , English Grade - 80-84.9%

10th 2014

> Karnataka , Kannada Grade - 90-94.9%

# **Projects**

senior system Engineer 153 Days

Collaborated with customers to help resolve issues and provide proactive assistance. Managed support issues. Worked with different teams to produce and deploy certificates Integrated different applications with IBM tools for providing authentication and authorization. Worked on logging frameworks like log4j. Tested different URLs and their flows with get and post requests.